Guide to the Stanford University, Haas Center for Public Service, Records SC0541
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2001-237
  - Service Learning at American Universities Files, Subseries 5
    - Kettering/ Public Leadership (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Indiana University (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Lafayette College (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Metropolitan State University (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Michigan State University (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Ohio Wesleyan University (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Rice University (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Rollins College (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Saint Joseph's (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Salisbury State University (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - San Diego State University (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco State University (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Santa Clara University (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Seattle University (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Southern Methodist University (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Stanford University (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - St. Norbet College (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - University of Illinois (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - University of Michigan (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - University of Minnesota (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Univ. of North Florida (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - University of Pennsylvania (unofficial) (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - University of Puget Sound (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - UCLA (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - UCLA Field Studies Program (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Univ. of California at San Fran (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - University of California - San Diego (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Univ. of California - Santa Cruz (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - University of Redlands (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - University of San Diego (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Stanford University (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Current Trends in Policy Making- Stanford Univ. '92-'93 Prof. Brady (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Issues in Leadership- Stanford Univ. '92-'93 School of Educ. (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Stanford University Curriculum on Children and Society (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Stanford Univ. Preparation for Internship Learning (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Stanford University Public Policy 182/ Urban Studies 135 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Stanford University American Studies 120, Process and … (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Study-Service Connections: Course Syllabi- Stanford (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Susquehanna University (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Tuft University (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - University of California Berkeley (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Univ. of Calif.-- Davis (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - University of Southern Calif. (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - University of Utah (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - University of Vermont (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - University of Virginia (unofficial) (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Vanderbilt University (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Wellesley College (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Western Michigan University (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Westmont College (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Wheaton College, Illinois (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Wittenberg College (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Wofford College (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Worcester Polytechnic Inst. (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Yale University (unofficial) (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Not able to participate (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Young Adolescents and Community Service June 1989 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - 'Eight Summers- Reflections on Lisle Programs: 1976-1983' (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Setting a research agenda for service learning' Jan. 1991 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Service-Learning in the South: higher Education and Public Service 1967-1972 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - "You Can't Learn it All on Campus" reprinted from Ebony Magazine, June 1972 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - "The Immediate Usefulness of Liberal Arts: Variations on a theme" (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Service Learning: Education for democracy' published in Public Education May/June (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Atlanta Service-Learning Conference Report 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 'The Educational Uses of the World: experiential learning & the Peace Corps' Dec. 1968 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 'The Dialogue between Volunteerism and Feminism: Implications for Higher Education' (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 'Overcoming Obstacles to Institutionalization of Experiential Learning Programs' (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - The National Center for public Service Internships (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 'Learning Outcomes: the measurement & evaluation of experiential learning' (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - An agenda for off-campus learning experiences Dec. 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Interlude Programs in U.S. Undergraduate Education Dec. 1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 'You're the Tutor' 1967 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Community Roles for Youth Publication June 1985, autumn 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 'Youth Participation: a concept paper' Dec. 31, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 'Workbook for Students in Community Services' 1975 Tim Stanton & Catherine Ritvo (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - A Social Work Education Program for Clinch Valley College and Southwest Virginia' 1970 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Clinch River Educational Cooperative (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Service Learning at Appalshop 198(?) article (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Clinch Valley College Service Learning 1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - East Tennessee State University Service- Learning 1949 article and info (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Georgia State College for Women Service-Learning articles 1946 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Highlander reports 50th Anniversary Celebration Edition Dec. 1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Picking Up the Pieces: Women in and Out of Work in the Rural South Publication, Jan. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - The Jellico Handbook: A Teachers Guide to Community-based Economics (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Oral histories by 'Community Development and the Economy" (SOC 410) students Spring 1987 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - 1993-95 HBCU Network Report- Service Learning Nov 1995 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - '85,000 Service Learners' Dec. '71 draft (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - 'An Advocate for Adolescents' (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - An introductory manual on youth participation for program administrators- Dept. Of Health 1976 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Resources for Youth newsletter 'These Young People Care!' Fall 1982 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - National Commission on Resources for Youth (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Virginia Water Project INC. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - FIPSE notes (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - FIPSE 1995 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - FIPSE/Public Service Scholars 1997 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - FIPSE proposal '93 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Hewlett 8/96 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - '94-'95 Hewlett Foundation (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Hewlett Service-Learning grant 1994-96, 1997-99 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Faculty Fund '91 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Rockefeller Foundation proposal (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Surdna Foundation (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Director's Files, Subseries 6
    - California Campus Compact 1995 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - California Campus Compact mailings (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - California Campus Compact mailing (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - California Campus Compact proposal to UC Regents 08/01/94 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - California Campus Compact proposal to the Corporation for National & Community Service (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - California Campus Compact 2Yr Plan by UC Regents (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Future of California Campus Compact 01/96 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - California Campus Compact biographical statements (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - California Campus Compact decentralized members (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - California Campus Compact 3rd Yr. Renewal request (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - California Campus Compact Website (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Advisory Board meetings 5/92 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Advisory Bd. Mtg. 5/23/93 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Advisory Board meeting 01/12/94 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Advisors May 1994 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Advisory Board meeting 01/20/95 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Haas Center Advocacy & Partisan Political Activity Policy (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Advisors 5/12-13/95 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Advisors' 1/16/96 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Advisors' meeting 5/96 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - 1/97 mid year meeting (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - NAB update 10/97 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Articles re: Milton recommendations 1983 & 1984 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Clearinghouse Connections Programs 1987 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - PSC & extra departmental programs 1984 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Centralizing internships 1985 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Public Service Center background history and Milestones 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - HCPS- Org. Location Issues (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - SIW (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Stanford in Washington location issues (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Faculty Steering Committee March 31, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Pilot Program to link public service & academic learning: proposal funded winter 1990 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Faculty Steering Committee meeting 12/05/89 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Faculty Steering Committee meeting 06/07/90 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Distinguished Public Service Award (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Faculty Steering Committee meeting, May 1989 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Faculty Steering Committee meeting 10/06/86 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - David Kennedy, Faculty Steering Committee Chair 1988-89 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Faculty Steering Committee mtng notes from 11/30/87 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Faculty Steering Committee 1987-88 members (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Public service and liberal arts ed proposal 1/30/87 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Faculty Steering Committee Mtg. 05/04/87 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Faculty Steering Committee meeting 02/13/87 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Public Service These house (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - PSC Committee on Objectives & Evaluation (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Proposal for adopting public service course (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Nov. 18, 1985 Faculty Steering Committee meeting (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Faculty Steering Committee November 27, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Faculty Steering Committee March 13, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Faculty Steering 12/91 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Faculty Steering 3/92 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Faculty Steering - Spring, 92 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - Faculty Steering Committee 11/5/92 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Faculty Steering Committee meeting 03/04/93 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Faculty Steering Committee 12/8/93 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Faculty Steering Committee - 3/7/94 Winter Qtr. meeting (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Faculty Steering Committee meeting Spring 1994 6/2/94 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - Faculty Steering Committee meeting (12/5/94) Fall 94 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - Faculty Steering Committee 3/95 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - Faculty Steering 6/95 (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Faculty Steering Committee November '96 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Faculty Steering Committee 3/13/96 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Steering 6/96 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Steering Committee Winter '97Faculty Steering Committee Feb. 25, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Steering Committee 3/1/99 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Steering Committee members (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Faculty Steering Committee materials (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - PSC fundraising info 1987-89 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Centennial (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - University Seminars 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - FIPSE 1988 Motivated to Serve (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Eastern Council 4/96 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 10th anniversary (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Colby seminars (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Garner Fellowship (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Anne Colby visit 1994-95 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Urban Studies 196 – Seminar in Community Organizing (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Org. culture/ values (readings) (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Visions/goals '95-'96 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Steering Committee 1986 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Other centers (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - HCPS gift opportunities 1993-94 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Commons, fall 1995 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - HCPS annual report 1992-93 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Reorganization (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Provost fund report (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Parker seminars/process (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Long range planning (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - The Commons, June 1994 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - PSC retreat 1986- follow-up (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - PSC orientation October 9, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Retreat January 22, 1988 follow-up (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Retreat planning --- 1991 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Fall retreat, 1988 core (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Fall 1987 retreat (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - 1989 fall retreat planning (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Retreat planning 1990 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Retreat-September 1992 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Retreat locations (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Nazir's workshop (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Nazir's workshop --- transparencies (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Staff retreat fall 1994 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - K-12 programs, S-L 2000 (1994) (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - HCPS retreat 9/95 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Summer Sessions Committee (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Mission/core values (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Materials from HCPS strategic planning process (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Stanford University personnel services strategic plan 03/93 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Strategic planning 1993-94 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Strategic planning 1993 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Alumni Association mentors (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Institute of International Studies Charter Draft 06/30/86 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Environmental Policy Program at Stanford in Washington (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - FIPSE/CSW '94 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Service Learning article- Stanford report 01/13/90 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Study Service Connections 1998-99 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Ethnic Outreach 1987-88 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Ethnic Outreach 88-89-90 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Curriculum on Children and Society '94-95 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network 1994-95 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Hewlett Foundation Grant 5/93 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Penney Foundation grant (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Children and Society curriculum creation (1992) (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Report on the Children and Society Curriculum 5/92 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Children and Society Curriculum Committee agenda/meetings (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Children and Society Curriculum committee materials (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Undergraduate Program in the School of Education (UPSE) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - UPSE maintenance issues (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Stanford-Cornell proposal on Teacher Ed for Mellon Foundation (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Learning by Integrating Curriculum and Service (LINCS) info packet (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - LINCS Service-Learning Course (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Undergraduate Special 120B: Racism ad Prejudice (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Course Proposal: 'The Unseen America' SPR. QTR. 1989 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Recommended standard practices for professorships, deanships, curatorships, and directorships (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Haas professorship search 1998- notes (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Haas Centennial Chair Nominees (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Haas professorship criteria for appointments draft (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Vandana Shiva (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Haas Centennial Chair nominees (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Blake, Herman J. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Shalala, Donna (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Cisneros, Henry (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Coles, Robert (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Dukakis, Michael (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Ehrlich, Thomas (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Phillip Lee (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Minnich, Elisabeth (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Moses, Robert (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - O'Neill, Paul (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Powell, John (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Reynoso, Cruz (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Shiva, Vandana (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Nadinne Strossen (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Bishop Tutu (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - West, Cornell (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Gaventa, John (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Havel, Vaclav (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Joseph, James (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Keene, Barry (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Kemmis Daniel (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Kohl, Herb (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Edelman, marian Wright (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Hills, Carla (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Kozal, Jonathan (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Education Abroad Program 1987 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Internships at other universities (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - PSC- oversees studies (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - DeWitt Wallace Readers Digest (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Pew Trust correspondence with Don Kennedy (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Proposal to Rockefeller Foundation (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - Proposal to Campus Opportunities Outreach League re: integrating service and learning (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Hoy survey (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - S-L proposal to a Stanford Forum on Public Service and Liberal Arts Ed 02/27/87 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Feminist Studies 101, Public Service Section (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Communications 01- Service Project Evaluations and thank-yous 1992 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Proposal for curriculum development funds linking public service to Comm 01 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Seminar: Urban Policy - Prof. Luis Fraga (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Feminist Studies 101 - Public Service section proposal 05/12/92 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - 'American Indian Ways of Knowing' (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - Grant proposal for community service writing project (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Science, Technology, and research at Stanford (STAR) proposal (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Feasibility study for a research course on the economic institutions of the inner city proposal 03/16/92 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Pilot programs linking public service to the curriculum notes (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Pilot project linking public service and the curriculum- funding info (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Service Across the curriculum: Options for Program Development Dec. 1991 (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Study-Service Connections/Community Research 1991-92 highlights (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Humanities and Sciences Service-Learning curriculum development funds application invitations (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - Pilot Fund to link Public Service and Academic Study Progress report 04/22/91 (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Pilot Fund linking public service and academic study renewal request 06/08/90 (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Pilot Fund renewal request 07/09/91 (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Pilot Fund to link public service and academic study renewal request 07/19/91 (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Soc. 107/207 proposal 01/26/90 (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Faculty Steering Committee endorsement of pilot program to link service and academic study 12/05/88 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - President's and Provost's Improvement Fund for Undergraduate Education Summer 1988 (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Linguistics 150 WTR 1991 (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Real Writing Project: evaluation of the first year (1998-89) (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Development of pilot fund linking public service and academic study (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - Urban Studies Program renewal 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Community Service Writing proposal (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - ECON 90- Intro to Financial Accounting (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - PSYCH 174 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Recommendations from the 2nd Senate ad hoc Committee on the Professoriate 05/17/90 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Community research/ practicum project 04/20/89 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Pilot Project to link public service and academic learning proposal response letters 02/90 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - History 162 A proposal (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Proposal to expand the "Real Writing" project 01/15/90 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 'Hoops, Hurdles, and Stumbling Blocks: Knowledge About Paths through High School' proposal (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - SOC 107: sociology of Mental Health proposal 01/08/90 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Classics proposal (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 'The Cultural Anthropology of the Southwest' proposal 01/08/90 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - CE 223- 'Architecture: Process and Practice' proposal 01/04/90 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - 'The Work of Art and the Creation of Mind' proposal 05/17/96 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Feminist Studies 104- Townsend (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Service Learning Initiative 1993-94 brochure (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Misc. Director documents (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - You Can Make a Difference Stall Series Vol. I, No. 4 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - HCPS self-guided tour (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Curriculum on children and society (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Haas Center Visiting Mentors program (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Moral Exemplars visit (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Moral Exemplars budgets (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Moral Exemplars- notes and misc. items (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Moral Exemplars events (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - brief bios of Moral Exemplars (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Kip Tiernan and Fran Froehlich visit 1995 spr. (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Kip Tienan vitae (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Fran Froehlich vitae (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Kip Tiernan articles (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - The poor People's United Fund (Tiernan and Froehlich) (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - E. Cabell Brand visit (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - E. Cabell Brand - biographical info (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - E. Cabell Brand organizations (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - E. Cabell Brand misc. info (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - E. Cabell Brand articles (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - East Palo Alto/ Stanford Summer Academy evaluation report: summer 1991 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - School Support Programs assessment report June 1993 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - HCPS annual report 1994 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Together We Accomplish More (TEAM) evaluation 1990-91 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - EPASSA student survey summer 1996 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Self-Evaluation and Student Empowerment: Plan for Ravenswood Stanford Tutoring Program 06/06/94 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - HCPS Student Leadership Development (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Spring 1990 community-building data collection 06/18/90 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - 1990 Leadership Summit (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - 1990 CPA Orientation (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - HCPS Issues (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Mentor Apparent Program (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Upward Bound Informational 10/11/90 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - TEM training 1990 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Jepson School of Leadership Studies (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Leaders Orientation Fall 1991 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Leadership Development Program- student suggestions (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Highlander Research and Education Center (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - National Clearinghouse for Leadership Program (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Student Leadership Opportunities survey (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Student Leadership Development 1992 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Stanford Upward Bound Evaluation 1998-99 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Schools programs evaluations 1998-99 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - PSC evaluation information October 1988 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - International interest in the Clearinghouse 03/03/88 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Summary of clearinghouse visitors from Sept. 29- Oct. 31, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - 'Making the Connection: A Workshop for Community Agencies' (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Results from Clearinghouse Community survey 05/23/88 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Results from Clearinghouse student survey 02/12/88 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Evaluation of the Clearinghouse and student internships 03/08/88 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Volunteers with elderly evaluation discussion (Box 13, Folder 68)